{
    "subject": "resource/Sultan_Mudzafar_Shah_I",
    "predicate": "ontology/title",
    "object": "Sultan of Kedah",
    "human_readable": "The title of Sultan Mudzafar Shah I is Sultan of Kedah.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9707509875297546,
            "question": "What is the title of Sultan Mudzafar Shah I?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9247729182243347,
            "question": "Who is Sultan Mudzafar Shah I?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9067888855934143,
            "question": "How is Sultan Mudzafar Shah I remembered by the people of Kedah?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8715354204177856,
            "question": "What is the significance of Sultan Mudzafar Shah I in Kedah's history?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7321454882621765,
            "question": "What kind of ruler was Sultan Mudzafar Shah I?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6162446141242981,
            "question": "Is there a specific time period associated with Sultan Mudzafar Shah I's reign?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5321758389472961,
            "question": "Over what region did Sultan Mudzafar Shah I rule?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5017241835594177,
            "question": "Were there any notable achievements or policies attributed to Sultan Mudzafar Shah I?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4988328218460083,
            "question": "Is there any information available about Sultan Mudzafar Shah I's personal life or family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.481323778629303,
            "question": "Are there any significant historical events associated with Sultan Mudzafar Shah I's rule?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The title of Sultan Mudzafar Shah I is Sultan of Kedah.",
            "html": "dbpedia_14_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information available about Sultan Mudzafar Shah I's personal life or family?",
            "html": "dbpedia_14_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any notable achievements or policies attributed to Sultan Mudzafar Shah I?",
            "html": "dbpedia_14_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Over what region did Sultan Mudzafar Shah I rule?",
            "html": "dbpedia_14_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_14_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_14_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_14_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_14_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_14_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_14_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_14_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_14_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_14_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_14_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the titles and history of various sultans, including Sultan Mudzafar Shah I. Specifically, it mentions that he founded the Sultanate of Kedah in 1136 and used the title \"Sultan Muzaffar Shah.\" Therefore, the statement that the title of Sultan Mudzafar Shah I is \"Sultan of Kedah\" is supported by the documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}